<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Fictional Maine Guide</string>

    <!--Selected location - Tool's hidden info-->
    <string name="fictionalLocationToolText">Fake Name, Maine</string>
    <string name="actualLocationToolText">Actual Location: Derp</string>
    <string name="locationInfoToolText">Blah blah blah information about this fictional location (movie/story/show/etc.). Then info on the actual location it\'s based off of.</string>
    <string name="webLinkToolText">www.ExampleWebsiteInfo.com</string>

    <!--TAB Names-->
    <string name="cabotCoveTab">Cabot Cove</string>
    <string name="derryTab">Derry</string>
    <string name="darkScoreLakeTab">Dark Score</string>
    <string name="littleTallIslandTab">Little Tall</string>

    <!--Fictional Location Names-->
    <string name="cabotCoveText">Cabot Cove, Maine</string>
    <string name="derryText">Derry, Maine</string>
    <string name="darkScoreLakeText">Dark Score Lake, Maine</string>
    <string name="littleTallIslandText">Little Tall Island, Maine</string>

    <!--Actual Location Names-->
    <string name="kennebunkportText">Actual Name: Kennebunkport, Maine</string>
    <string name="bangorText">Actual Name: Bangor, Maine</string>
    <string name="flagstaffText">Actual Name: Flagstaff Lake, Maine</string>
    <string name="southwestHarborText">Actual Name: Southwest Harbor, Maine</string>

    <!--Location Descriptions-->
    <string name="cabotCoveInfo">Murder, She Wrote is an American crime drama television series starring Angela Lansbury as mystery writer and amateur detective Jessica Fletcher. The show revolves around the day-to-day life of Jessica Fletcher, a childless, widowed, retired English teacher who becomes a successful mystery writer. Despite fame and fortune, Jessica remains a resident of Cabot Cove, a small coastal community in Maine, and maintains her links with all of her old friends, never letting her success go to her head. \n \nThe fictional \"Cabot Cove\" name for the series\' coastal town was derived from the name of an actual bay harbor inlet in Kennebunkport, Maine, located near the town\'s center, on the road where motels and lobster shack dives are located. Kennebunkport is known for its beaches, including long, sandy Goose Rocks Beach and smaller Arundel Beach.</string>
    <string name="derryInfo">Derry is a fictional town and a part of Stephen King\'s fictional Maine topography. Derry has served as the primary setting for a number of his stories such as: IT, Insomnia, Bag of Bones, Dreamcatcher, Fair Extension, 11/22/63, and more. King has acknowledged that Derry is actually his portrayal of Bangor, Maine. \n \nBangor is located in Penobscot County. Bangor has a port of entry at Bangor International Airport, also home to the Bangor Air National Guard Base. Bangor has a humid continental climate, with cold, snowy winters, and warm summers. Outdoor activities in the Bangor City Forest and other nearby parks, forests, and waterways include hiking, sailing, canoeing, hunting, fishing, skiing, and snowmobiling.</string>
    <string name="darkScoreLakeInfo">Dark Score Lake, Maine is specifically referenced in Stephen King\'s Bag of Bones. Another part of this story takes place in Castle Rock, Maine, which holds an important linked role in many of Stephen King\'s stories. Castle Rock is a fictional location, taking details from the actual location of Woodland, Maine. \n \nDark Score Lake\'s actual location is known as Flagstaff Lake, Maine. Flagstaff Lake is located in Somerset County and Franklin County, Maine. The lake\'s surface area is 20,300 acres. It is extremely shallow, with the deepest point at 48 feet. Landlocked salmon and brook trout can be caught here. Some points on the lake are very marshy and have to be negotiated with a canoe or kayak; even then, wading may be necessary in the marshy areas to get through to the rest of the lake.</string>
    <string name="littleTallIslandInfo">Little Tall Island, Maine is the primary setting for both Stephen King\'s Dolores Claiborne and Storm of the Century. Weather it\'s a devastating winter storm, or a total solar eclipse, these tight-knit communities fester beings with sinister plots. \n \nLittle Tall Island is a fictional version of Southwest Harbor, Maine. Southwest Harbor is a town in Hancock County, Maine. Side note: Hancock is referenced in Stephen King\'s Pet Cemetery, fictionally known as Ludlow, Maine. \n \nSouthwest Harbor is located on Mount Desert Island. It is the largest municipality on the southwestern “quiet side” of the island. It is thought to be a historically romantic icon of seafaring coastal life, and is ranked as one of the top ten commercial fishing harbors in the state of Maine. Some of the world’s most spectacular sailboats and yachts are built by more than ten boat builders on the island. The small town has some great shops, galleries, eateries, and accommodations, plus many people enjoy Acadia National Park for its relaxed setting.</string>

    <!--Location Web Links-->
    <string name="cabotCoveLink">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Murder,_She_Wrote</string>
    <string name="derryLink">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Derry_(Stephen_King)</string>
    <string name="darkScoreLink">http://stephenkingsmaine.com/dark-score-lake</string>
    <string name="littleTallLink">https://www.kingsleighinn.com/southwestharborinformation.html</string>

</resources>
